## **Orly Guerra**

**Summary** 

Technical Communication major with computing language experience in Java, C++, and Swift. Strong academic, communicative, and interpersonal skills. Dedicated, self motivated, and willing to learn more to better my own and others' understandings of the world.

Skills

Proficient in Microsoft Office, Adobe Creative Cloud, Camtasia, iWork, and adaptive learning to computer software and hardware. Strong communication skills and adaptable to various social environments.

**Education** 

University of North Texas • B.S. Technical Communication August 2017 - December 2022 (Expected Graduation Date), Denton, TX

**Employment Experience** 

**UNT Housing and Residence Life** • Resident Assistant

**AUGUST 2021 - PRESENT** 

Serving as a community builder with residents and a liaison between residents and Housing.

**H-E-B** ● Software Engineer Intern

MAY 2021 - JULY 2021, DLS

Developed an iOS application utilizing SwiftUI in a collaborative environment on the DLS Team.

**UNT Technical Communications Tech Lab** • Lab Assistant

JANUARY 2020 - MAY 2021

Honed presentation and communication skills by assisting students and instructors with software skills.

H-E-B • CSA, Checker, Self-Checkout & Gas Station Attendant

JUNE 2016 - PRESENT, Corporate #480 Currently on educational leave of absence.

**Honors** 

The National Society Of Leadership And Success Member UNT Chapter (April 2020 - Present)
H-E-B Hospitality Partner of the Month (October 2018)
H-E-B Partner of the Month (June 2018)

UNT Honors College Member (August 2017 - Present)

References

Rene Hernandez H-E-B Service Manager, Corp #618 (210) 274-4134 s6188m@heb.com

Megan Eyden Financial Service Business Owner (210) 397-5242 meganeyden@gmail.com

Dr. Deidre Lannon Texas State History Professor (512) 245-2142 dl24@txstate.edu